A lot of gurus online are saying that
if you're not using AI right now in your
business, you're falling behind.
And if you were to use AI, and if you
were to use this prompt, and you're like,
"I
get it." However, using AI is a big thing,
but also it's not as amazing as
everyone makes out. First of all,
the ChatGPT app is just unreal,
and the dictate function I'll show you in
a second.
But in this video,
I'm going to explain why this book cover
helped me rebrand a
supplement company's business,
and how you can use it to benefit your own
business
and product sales.
There's a little microphone just next to
the prompt thing here.
I've just walked past a Lamborghini
Huracan Sterrato.
It's 566,000 Australian dollars.
If I was to buy this
and finance it with a balloon payment at
the end of, say,
$300,000 in three years,
what would my weekly repayments look
like at the current interest rates for car
finance at the moment in New South Wales
in Australia?
So every time I have a thought,
whatever it is, I just get ChatGPT to
do the thinking for me. Now,
this isn't always 100% accurate,
but it gives me some
rough ideas. Weekly repayments,
2,000 Australian dollars.
So last week,
I did a one-to-one with a chap who owns
this company.
Now,
I'm going to put a link to his supplement
business in the description in case
some of you think, "Oh my God,
that sounds really interesting.
I'm going to buy some." I did have some
problems right from the onset, which was
the name of the supplements.
So we have one here called Flexibility
Booster, and as
you can see here, collagen, glucosamine,
and something else that helps
with joint health. And it says here,
"Strengthens joints,
allows you to return to
activities without discomfort." But
when I see Flexibility Booster, I don't
think of moving more, being pain-free.
I think of a hormone
that women produce during pregnancy called
relaxin, which
means they can be at higher susceptible
risk of dislocations.
So I feel like the name
is maybe a little bit off. Second product,
Joint Jumper.
Helps lower inflammation to alleviate
joint discomfort.
And again, two compounds here.
Chap in question
that runs this business is a
pharmacist, so he knows his stuff. I hope.
Again, Joint Jumper,
I couldn't resonate with that as a
potential natural alternative to
ibuprofen.
When you think about lowering
inflammation, I think ibuprofen.
I also think that I don't really know what
inflammation is.
Then the third product,
which he says he wasn't massive on
priority at the moment,
was Omega 3. Now,
there's a lot of information online about
the benefits of Omega
3, and straightaway I said to him,
podcast clips, people like Rhonda Patrick,
Chris
Williamson talking about the benefits.
Now, the second I saw these,
some of you might have seen my clips I've
been putting
on Instagram recently, my ADHD brain,
[mimicking explosions] .
And this is one of the best books
that I've ever read.
It's also got one of the best covers I've
ever seen.
You'll notice that the name of the book
is up here, and the biggest part of the
book is just the status play Fair Play
Will Store. Amazing.
That's the best book cover I've ever seen.
So what do I do?
This is where I go to ChatGPT.
I'm designing a supplement
which I want to bring
out.
I really like the branding of this book.
Using this book as inspiration,
create me a bottle, design of pills
that says,
"This fixes joint and pains." Now,
originally, straightaway,
the image it creates
here, as you can see,
"This fixes joints and pains,"
and it got the structure of it
slightly wrong, but it
was amazing how quick it came up with
this.
So I said, "Amazing.
Please now change the title." Made it very
easy for AI to
understand. Boom. Using this
and just a simple prompt, I've
now managed to design potential new
packaging, and again, this doesn't
have to be what he runs with, but to me,
this is just such a smart thing.
Out of a whole shelf
or a whole online store.
This fixes joints and pains. Amazing.
Evidence-based formula to joint health.
We can put the ingredients
and whatever on the back. Great.
Then the other one in question,
the Joint Jumper, I just created this.
Better than ibuprofen.
They know what it is.
They know what it's going to do.
A natural alternative to ibuprofen.
Those two things would not only sell
themselves a lot easier, but
when we look at
the marketplace at the moment,
maybe things like TikTok Shop,
creators would love
this product because they could pick it up
and say, "These pills here said they
were better than ibuprofen.
I took them for a week,
and I can tell you the truth,
they are better than ibuprofen." Now,
I know TikTok Shop
is a bit of a wild place
at the moment.
I even considered making this the
thumbnail.
And actually, as a curveball,
why don't we design the thumbnail for this
video
whilst you're here using AI? I mean,
that makes sense, doesn't it?
So if we go to YouTube,
I actually think
that I've got a book cover
that we can run with. Okay,
so we did a book with "The 4-Hour
Workweek." This one
got a lovely click-through rate,
so I'm just going to copy that.
I'm going to go into my other YouTube
browser. Don't ask. I said don't ask,
right?
Basically,
this page should have a vidIQ plugin,
which means that I can
steal this. Cool. So I've downloaded that.
We are going to go over to Mr.
ChatGPT. I can go here, upload. Here
is a thumbnail
that worked pretty well on my YouTube
channel.
What I would love is
if you could swap the books to put
Will Store's cover where this one is,
so it looks
like I am holding the first book I
mentioned
in this thread. Yeah, I'm showing off.
Let's see how Mr. ChatGPT's going.
It could be female, you never know.
Apparently, saying please and thank you
is wasting millions of dollars.
Listen,
if you don't think these robots
are taking count of manners, you're
wrong. This could not work, by the way.
And if it doesn't,
we're going to have to go into Photoshop
and try to work some
magic. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let me stop you there.
It's putting the supplement in it with it,
isn't it?
Okay,
we're going to have to go for a whole new
bloody prompt here, aren't we?
Okay, I have attached two images. One
is a thumbnail.
However,
I would like to swap the title to the
image to
anything could happen right now.
Now it's creating the image.
One of the issues that we see here is
that it's creating it portrait, which is
going to be a bit of a bloody issue
considering I sent it to ChatGPT
landscape. But we can work on it. What
are you doing?
Okay, whatever's happening here,
it ain't working.
That's the wrong cover, mate.
Do you know what?
Let's just try Photoshopping this.
Here's the thumbnail I
was creating for someone earlier on.
Okay, let's put this one here. Okay,
first of all, let's try a bit of AI.
So I've highlighted the book in question.
I said, "Please,
can you make this white?" I have no idea
what's going on here.
Isn't it crazy?
We're making a thumbnail for a video
inside the video.
It's like "Inception." Let's try this
again. I'm getting pissed off now.
Let's just try generative fill.
Let's just see what happens here.
Just see what happens here. Maybe it
was my prompt.
What the fuck are you doing here, mate?
Remove cover and make plain white book.
Why is AI pissing me off today?
Tell you what we might do as well.
Who's that? What is going on there, mate?
Okay, let's try this. This
is doing my head in.
Okay,
what's probably going to be important here
is the hands.
So let's copy that as a mask. Copy
that as a mask.
It's not terrible. Now,
what we could do here, I suppose,
is maybe we
get these layers, as in the fingers,
and we just give them a little bit of a,
maybe
even a bit of a dark outer glow.
Let's see if this cleans it up a bit.
The only thing about this image of the
book is it looks a little bit too clean,
doesn't it? Well,
that's the one There we go. See that?
How we just get the light down a little
bit.
That just for some reason just makes it
look legitimate.
I love that.
Do we get a bit of an outer glow on it as
well?
Oh, a little bit of an outer glow. Cool.
So now we can start to think about
packaging for this.
And again, my golden rule
is do the packaging last. I know that.
So I say we'll go to thumbsup.tv.
I made this using AI.
Do you know what could be a good play
here? Just throwing this out there.
I know everything's going a little bit
crazy at the moment.
Can you remove the name Will Store
and instead put
James Smith?
Just thought we could be making things a
little bit too complex,
but I know this is going to seem like an
abhorrent amount of time to spend on
packaging, but just remember,
if they don't click, they don't watch,
and if
they don't watch, what's the point?
Got two ChatGPTs here working.
I don't like what's happened with the
fingers here, mate.
I don't like what's going on there.
Whose hairline is that?
All right,
we've gone from baseball cap to that.
I have a feeling this one might cook it up
a bit better. Come on. Come on, ChatGPT.
You got this. Come on. Oh,
this looks better, don't it?
I bet there's some Photoshop whiz that
are like, "Mate,
you're doing it all wrong.
Could do it way better." Probably.
You're probably right, mate.
So what we're going to do now
is just kind of make the cover disappear a
little
bit, like these are the levels. These
are the levels, mate.
I'm not even sure I fucking like this
anymore. Go back to thumbsuptv.
How ChatGPT will change marketing forever.
Marketing your business. Cool.
I think that's quite a good one.
So there you can see even how I created
the
packaging for this using AI.
We've got Photoshop that's got the
built-in generative fill.
We've got ChatGPT.
This is not good enough to have ideas for
you.
So imagine this is an accessory as
something that you have
that you can utilize to
do thinking for you, calculations for you.
Even little things like this.
My twin brother earns 100,000 pounds a
year. He is employed.
I am self-employed and earn the same.
We are both...
I don't have a twin brother.
Meeting in Dubai from London.
The flights are 500 pound business class.
I am able to write mine off as we're
meeting someone
about a future business. He isn't.
What is the difference in real life
costs between us? Then here again,
we can see because of his
inability to create tax deduction,
the real cost to him is
8,000 pounds for the 3,500 pounds flight
because he has to pay tax on the income
that he earns before making it.
We even get a breakdown.
So it's 4,260 pounds cheaper to be
self-employed and to travel business.
That's why the most people
that travel business class
are self-employed.
Again, here's another thing.
I have a budget of 800,000 pounds to buy a
house.
In the UK, I could do so with a 20 year,
or let's go 30 year.
How much does it really cost me?
Please include stamp
duty and post-tax income. Also include
interest paid over that time.
If I bought in Dubai and lived in
Dubai and paid no tax,
what it costs me there.
So a lot of people don't really realize
that if you want to buy an 800,000 pound
house,
it costs actually a lot more than
that because you have to earn the money to
then pay tax to then have the money.
So your real cost here to buy a house of
800,000 pounds is
actually 1.5 million. Actually,
not even that. Here you go.
You'd need 2.3 million pre-tax to afford
the 1.5 million
cost. So you buy 800K property.
It's really costing you
2.3 million over 30 years because you've
got to earn the money, pay tax on it.
So then, say you do a mortgage in Dubai,
you need 1.5 million.
So when you look at the actual money you
would need to live in Dubai, you would
need nearly a million less pounds because
you wouldn't have to pay tax and give
money to it. Where you pay tax, you,
in essence, have a wealth bucket with a
massive hole in the bottom,
and every time you fill up the bucket,
half falls out,
47% if you're in Australia.
So here you go.
You need to earn 800,000 pounds more in
the UK than Dubai over 30 years.
That's 27,000 pounds more in earnings just
to afford the same thing.
This is where theory and theoretic
and mathematics can be utilized to make
decisions. Here's one for you.
One more before we go.
If I sell my business in three years for
150 million,
let's go dollars,
and I have 10% of the shares at
that point, I live in
Australia, but if I moved to Dubai,
how much tax would I
save if I moved there for the two years
required?
Please let me know how many US dollars I
would,
in essence,
save a day across those two years.
So I would save 4,825 US dollars a day to
move to
Dubai. That's why people are moving there.
Gary Economics is like, "Oh,
tax the rich." But he worked in Japan for
a bit, and
he paid taxes in Japan. Why?
Because he lived there.
So if you move to Dubai,
it's your prerogative, of course.
I would be incentivized 5,000 US dollars a
day to move there.
Not to mention other income just to go
there.
That's what I would save, which
is pretty appealing.
That means that every week I'd have enough
to buy another investment property, and
I could do that every week. Anyway,
calculations, an extra brain.
Don't say to ChatGPT,
"Give me a viral idea for a video,"
because it's not that
good at that.
But for other stuff like this,
it's amazing.
Habibi, welcome to Dubai.
If you enjoyed this video,
you should definitely watch
this one here because, well,
YouTube thinks you're going to love it